Guide to the Papers of Peter Koch, 1974-2003 M1584
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series IV. JOB FILES, CHRONOLOGICAL
  - Job files, 1996
    - Gleeson Library Associates Fall Meeting; #unknown (Carton 14)
    - Barry Giffard - "The Surrealists Come to California"; #641 (Carton 14)
    - H. Derange Broadside - "Like Revolution, Love Betrays Itself First"; #642 (Carton 14)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Annual Meeting Keepsake; # 643 (Carton 14)
    - Friends of the Bancroft Library and 9th Annual Meeting Keepsake; #644 (Carton 14)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Fall Meeting Keepsake; #645 (Carton 14)
    - John Windle B.C.; #646 (Carton 14)
    - Stanford Univ. Libraries Hol. Card and Ep; #647 (Carton 14)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Xmas Card; #648 (Carton 14)
    - Buckaroo Real Lead Letterpress Coaster; #649 (Carton 14)
    - "Yao-Fens Kitchen" Coasters; #650 (Carton 14)
    - Pietrafessa / Danner moving and New Years cards and ep; #651 (Carton 14)
    - "Tango of the Scar: An End of the Century Epigram"-Juvenal Acosta; #652 (Carton 14)
    - The Book Club of CA - Bonda Lewis Announcement; #653 (Carton 14)
    - Patty Kidder Bailey Mem. Announcement and Ep; #654 (Carton 14)
    - "Printers to the Club Portfolio" Announcement; #655 (Carton 14)
    - Bucks Last Wreck - David E. Thomas; #656 (Carton 14)
    - Eliot Holtzman Stat. (2 versions); #657 (Carton 14)
    - The visit by President Fernando Henrique Cardosa to the S.F. Bay Area Pamphlet; #658 (Carton 14)
    - John Windle Ad (For Quarterly NL); #659 (Carton 14)
    - The Book Club of CA - Quarterly N. Letter - Vol LXII #1 - Winter 1997; #660 (Carton 14)
    - Thomas Edwin Woodhouse bookplates: Thomas Edwin Woodhouse/Casa Madera Woodhouse; #661 (Carton 14)
    - Antiquarian Booksellers Assoc. of Am. Guide; #662 (Carton 14)
    - Kaiya (listed as Eliot) Holtzman Birth Announcement and Ep.; #663 (Carton 14)
    - William J. Monihan Mem. Card rep.; #664 (Carton 14)
    - Francis Edward Bullimore Memorial; #665 (Carton 14)
    - J. Curtis Taylor and TJ Thelma J-Jeanne Taylor B.C.; #666 (Carton 14)
    - Mrs. Eaves typographic specimen booklet (migr); #667 (Carton 14)
    - Holtzman Stationery; # 1375 (Carton 16)
    - Gleeson Library Associates stationery; #1225 (Carton 18)
    - Io Bonini Invitation; #668 (Carton 27)
    - Williams/Stacy Wedding Invitation and Ep. RSVP Card and Ep. (4pc.); #669 (Carton 27)
    - Aris Demetrios Sculpt. Install. Invitation; #670 (Carton 27)
    - Wilkinson / Peterson Wedding Invitation and Ep.; #671 (Carton 27)
    - Iris Weiner Party Invitation; #672 (Carton 27)
    - Artists Book Council Spring Quarterly Announcement; #673 (Carton 27)
    - Imprint B.C. (P. Tsang Design); #675 (Carton 27)
    - Oscar Lewis Photo Caption for Book Club; #676 (Carton 27)
    - Artists Book Council Dinner and Book Talk Invitation, RSVP card and Ep.; #677 (Carton 27)
    - Felt / Pineda Wedding Invit and Ep.; #678 (Carton 27)
    - Pacific Book Auction; #1027 (Carton 27)
    - Book Plate; #1019 (Carton 27)
    - Stephanie Alioto Wilhelm Mem. and Thank you Card; #674 (Carton 27)
  - Job files, 1997
    - Tribal Arts EP; #1220 (Carton 18)
    - Burton Weiss B.C. and 2 Stat. and 2 Ep.; #681 (Carton 27)
    - Bancroft Award; #1322 (Carton 27)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Stationery; #1332 (Carton 27)
    - Friendly Bancroft Council Statement; #1352 (Carton 27)
    - Goldyne Stationery; #1346 (Carton 27)
    - USF Mission Reprint; #1372 (Carton 27)
    - USF Mission; #1370 (Carton 27)
    - Bancroft Charles Faulhaber Stationery; #1359 (Carton 27)
    - "Swift Current Time" Vic Charlo; #680 (Carton 27)
    - "En Un Lugar De La Sangre" Valerie Young (Carton 27)
    - "Grove Traditions" Bohemian club Booklet; #682 (Carton 27)
    - Stephen Ducat business cards; #683 (Carton 27)
    - Consulate of Brazil in SF Booklet: "The Fernando Henrique Cardoso Administrations Human Rights Policy"; #684 (Carton 27)
    - Bohemian Club 125th Anniversary Keepsake; #685 (Carton 27)
    - Book Club of California - Quarterly Newsletter; #686 (Carton 27)
    - Quarterly Newsletter Vol. XII - #2; #687 (Carton 27)
    - Reichardt/Van Heusden Wedding (Announcement, EP, Part, Sm. Card); #688 (Carton 27)
    - Barroll/McMillan Wedding (Angel Williams Design); #689 (Carton 27)
    - Brown/Schnider Wedding (Wilstead and Taylor Design); #690 (Carton 27)
    - Kim Noble/Farmer Wedding Announcement and ep and card; #691 (Carton 27)
    - Bohemian Club Poster/Broadside; #692 (Carton 27)
    - Brayman/Hackel Bookplate; #693 (Carton 27)
    - Ben and Janet Calvin Card; #694 (Carton 27)
    - Friends of SFPL - Dan Carr Lecture Announcement, Postcard; #695 (Carton 27)
    - Chris Ritter Wedding; #696 (Carton 27)
    - "Congress for the New Urbanism" Manifesto - Peter Katz; #697 (Carton 27)
    - Wilsted and Taylor: Promo Brochure and Summer Party Invitation; #698 (Carton 27)
    - Bass/Walrod Wedding; #699 (Carton 27)
    - Lynn/Kenji Wedding/Peter; #700 (Carton 27)
    - "The Smile at the Foot of the Ladder" Lawrence Fixel; #701 (Carton 27)
    - American Printing History Assoc. Announcement #702 (Carton 27)
    - Gerbode Foundation business cards; #703 (Carton 27)
    - Novakov Project - Veiled Histories (Design Only); #704 (Carton 27)
    - Ann Whipple Parents Stationary; #706 (Carton 27)
    - David Roe Bookplate; #707 (Carton 27)
    - Steven Ducat Business Cards and Brochure; #708 (Carton 27)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Autumn Meeting Keepsake; #709 (Carton 27)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Autumn Meeting Announcement; #710 (Carton 27)
    - John Windle "With Compliments" Card; #711 (Carton 27)
    - Book Club of California - Nokai Yazhie Bookplate, Mike Harrison; #712 (Carton 27)
    - David Trachtenberg Business Cards, Stationary and Marlins Label (Not Printed); #713 (Carton 27)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Annual Meeting Keepsake; #714 (Carton 27)
    - Lisa Demetrios New Years Card; #715 (Carton 27)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Letters R.E. Missed Jobs; #716 (Carton 27)
    - Shiramizu Letterhead 96/97; #996 (Carton 28)
    - Sean Thackrey; #1006 (Carton 28)
    - Curtiss Taylor Xmas Cards; #1014 (Carton 28)
    - Jeannie Sack Business Cards; #1015 (Carton 28)
    - Artist Book Council (Carton 28)
    - Reichardt and Associates; #1021 (Carton 28)
    - Zipkin; #1022 (Carton 28)
    - Kick-Ass Coaster; #1041 (Carton 28)
    - Brayman/ Steve Hackel Bookplate; #1084 (Carton 28)
    - METIER (Tsang) Imprint; #1175 (Carton 28)
    - QNL #2; #1176 (Carton 28)
    - QNL #1 Fall 1997; #1177 (Carton 28)
    - Koch Post-Halloween Party; #1178 (Carton 28)
    - Stanford Xmas Card; #123 (Carton 28)
  - Job files, 1998
    - Gleeson Library Associates Christmas; #1057 (Carton 15)
    - Stanford Christmas Card; #1221 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates/ EPS; #1305 (Carton 28)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Stationary Sept.; #1330 (Carton 28)
    - Bancroft Award; #1321 (Carton 28)
    - Bancroft Cards; #1353 (Carton 28)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Spring Annual Meeting (Carton 28)
    - John Windle File - Card and Compliments (Carton 28)
    - Westward Bound Exhibit; #974 (Carton 28)
    - Bill Stout/ Jennings Project #1381 (Carton 28)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Annual Meeting Announcement; #980 (Carton 28)
    - Hinckle SF Award Print Only/ No Design; #981 (Carton 28)
    - Holtzman Brochure; #982 (Carton 28)
    - David Nelson/Kitchen Sisters; #984 (Carton 28)
    - Masatoshi/ Japonesque; #1003 (Carton 28)
    - Mas Mirielle; #1004 (Carton 28)
    - Einzig Memorial; #1007 (Carton 28)
    - APHA Announcement; #1008 (Carton 28)
    - QNL Summer; #1009 (Carton 28)
    - Bianca Calahesi Wedding Invitations and Reply Cards; #1010 (Carton 28)
    - Malloy/Auerbach Quote/ Peter Hanff; #1017 (Carton 28)
    - Flying Cloud Mills College; #1023 (Carton 28)
    - Lucente/Bookmarks; #1024 (Carton 28)
    - Cricket/ Book Poems (Canceled Job); #1025 (Carton 28)
    - Casalini/ Stanford Keepsake June; #1028 (Carton 28)
    - QNL SP; #1030 (Carton 28)
    - WNL Couer Art; #1036 (Carton 28)
    - Mills Film, Invite w/ EP, etc.; #1037 (Carton 28)
    - Colleen Bourke Wedding Invitations; #1038 (Carton 28)
    - Koch Halloween Party Invitation; #1040 (Carton 28)
    - Real West Coaster; #1042 (Carton 28)
    - UC Class Project: "The Last Words of Arthur Rimbaud"/ Barry Gifford tests; #1047 (Carton 28)
    - Novakov; #1048 (Carton 28)
    - K. Raff Wedding; #1049 (Carton 28)
    - Jonathan Gilmore; #1064 (Carton 29)
    - Japonesque Poster Masatosai; #1066 (Carton 29)
    - Elliot Porter Card; #1067 (Carton 29)
    - Albert De Silver 17 pelicans poem; #1068 (Carton 29)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Winter meeting Keepsake; #1070 (Carton 29)
    - Sharafian Bookplate; #1071 (Carton 29)
    - Book of Life; #1072 (Carton 29)
    - Baptist Homes; #1073 (Carton 29)
    - Artist Book Council; #1181 (Carton 29)
    - Novakov/Public Safety; #1089 (Carton 29)
    - Gleeson/Lawrence Ferlinghetti; #1090 (Carton 29)
    - Carnal Pleasures; #1115 (Carton 29)
    - QNL Fall; #1116 (Carton 29)
    - McCalister/Mark Livingston Memorial; #1180 (Carton 29)
    - Goldwasser ADS and Covers; #1183 (Carton 29)
    - Lucente Cards; #1185 (Carton 29)
    - Beth Hours; #1186 (Carton 29)
    - Sean Thackery: Orion tune; #1199 (Carton 29)
    - Laurie Thompson/ Thomas Schwartz; #1200 (Carton 29)
    - Tribal Arts; #1206 (Carton 29)
  - Job files, 1999
    - Gleeson Library Associates Fall Meeting; #unknown (Carton 15)
    - G.B. Carson Cards; #unknown (Carton 15)
    - Karen Eng; #unknown (Carton 15)
    - Antiquarian Booksellers Association; #unknown (Carton 15)
    - Doreen Schmid; #unknown (Carton 15)
    - Karen Schein; #unknown (Carton 15)
    - Stanford Bookplate commemorating Bing Wing; #unknown (Carton 15)
    - Stanford Invitation Design; #unknown (Carton 15)
    - Anne Kohs Business; #1344 (Carton 15)
    - Mondavi; #1333 (Carton 15)
    - Stanford Art and Negs; #1345 (Carton 15)
    - Bancroft Library and Friends Stationery; #1361 (Carton 15)
    - The Book Club of CA - Stationery; #1348 (Carton 15)
    - The Roxburghe Club; #1043 (Carton 15)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Spring Meeting Announcement; #1051 (Carton 15)
    - "Antoninus on Antoninus" Bancroft Books; #1052 (Carton 15)
    - Cincone Birth Announcement; #1053 (Carton 15)
    - Mankas Inverness Lodge; #1058 (Carton 15)
    - Koch - Wayzgoose; #1060 (Carton 15)
    - Rick Kennedy; #1061 (Carton 15)
    - Ann Hackel Birth Announcement; #1062 (Carton 15)
    - Philip Whalen Broadside; #1074 (Carton 15)
    - Stanford/Rice Presentation Sheet; #1075 (Carton 15)
    - Holtzman Birth Announcement; #1076 (Carton 15)
    - Party Invitation - Koch; #1077 (Carton 15)
    - Mary Jane Shanagher; #1078 (Carton 15)
    - Lucia Eames; #1079 (Carton 15)
    - Demetrios Wedding Announcement; #1080 (Carton 15)
    - Thomas Naber; #1081 (Carton 15)
    - Verlaine Fine Art; #1082 (Carton 15)
    - Koch Party; #1085 (Carton 15)
    - Stanford Reprint; #1086 (Carton 15)
    - Troy Daeton; #1087 (Carton 15)
    - Peter Coyote Poem; #1088 (Carton 15)
    - Eames; #1091 (Carton 15)
    - Graham Wedding; #1092 (Carton 15)
    - Stanford Library Opening; #1118 (Carton 15)
    - For Oonash Poems; #1141 (Carton 15)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Fall Meeting; #1187 (Carton 15)
    - Marhs - Schmitz New Year; #1195 (Carton 15)
    - Pisani Bookplate; #1210 (Carton 15)
    - Stanford Program; #1229 (Carton 15)
    - Stanford Holiday Card; #1238 (Carton 15)
    - Tribal Arts; #1219 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Christmas Card; #1226 (Carton 18)
  - Job files, 2000
    - Positive/Negative Box; no number (Carton 16)
    - Positive/Negative Box; no number (Carton 16)
    - Positive/Negative Catalog; no number (Carton 16)
    - Hard Words Invitation MSU; no number (Carton 16)
    - Montana Exhibition; #1336 (Carton 16)
    - Barbara Van Winkle; #1339 (Carton 16)
    - Artist Book Council; no number (Carton 16)
    - Kanter Lecture UCLA, March 18, 2000; no number (Carton 16)
    - Stanford Orchid Bookplate 5.0; no number (Carton 16)
    - Stanford 2000 bid; no number (Carton 16)
    - Koch Plates, Pricelist; #1341
    - Sharafian; #1356 (Carton 16)
    - Hormone Derang Portfolio; #1347 (Carton 16)
    - David Grishaver; #1340 (Carton 16)
    - Filter Party Invitations; no number (Carton 16)
    - Mills-Larkmead Adv; no number (Carton 16)
    - Artists Book council Brochure; no number (Carton 16)
    - Bancroft Award; no number (Carton 16)
    - Matlack Birth Announcements; no number (Carton 16)
    - Book Club Postcard- Western Bookds Exhibition, March 2000; no number (Carton 16)
    - Richard Gordon; no number (Carton 16)
    - Designer Bookbinders-Gleeson Library; no number (Carton 16)
    - Nancy Hoyt/ Susan Filter Christmas; no number (Carton 16)
    - Jeanie Sack; no number (Carton 16)
    - Beatrice Bowles; no number (Carton 16)
    - Sperisen Memorial 6.0; no number (Carton 16)
    - Chance Memorial; no number (Carton 16)
    - Nancy Hoyt; MIBBS; no number (Carton 16)
    - Colleen Bouille Beiger Birth Announcement; no number (Carton 16)
    - Ann Whipple Keepsake; no number (Carton 16)
    - Stanford Bookplate- Ludwig Lauerhass; no number (Carton 16)
    - Barchas/ Slipcase/Stanford; no number (Carton 16)
    - Fairfull Wedding Announcements; No number (Carton 16)
    - Gerbode Foundation; no number (Carton 16)
    - Gerbode Foundation, no number (Carton 16)
    - Stanford/Caspar Bookplate; no number (Carton 16)
    - QNL Vol. LXVI, No. 1 Winter 2000; #1314 (Carton 16)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Letterhead; #1328 (Carton 16)
    - UC Certificate "B" 1999/2000; #1327 (Carton 16)
    - Holtzman Christmas; #1376 (Carton 16)
    - Logos Project/ Hard Words, Portfolio and Prints; # 1334 (Carton 16)
    - Emmy Werner Bookplate; # 1109 (Carton 16)
    - Mills/Olen Library Bookplate; # 1110 (Carton 16)
    - La Filters Valentine; #1111 (Carton 16)
    - Bruce Walker Bookplate; #1113 (Carton 16)
    - William Abrahams Book; #1117 (Carton 16)
    - Holtzman 1999/2000, Dear Parents; #1373 (Carton 16)
    - Holtzman Stationery; # 1374 (Carton 16)
    - Becky F.- Creeley; #1194 (Carton 16)
    - Jeanette Hodge Wedding; #1196 (Carton 16)
    - Jeffrey Filter Invitations; # 1197 (Carton 17)
    - Stanford Imprint, Fall/Winter 2000/2001; #1202 (Carton 17)
    - Marlene Saritzky Stationary; #1203 (Carton 17)
    - Tom Koch Award (personal); #1204 (Carton 17)
    - Caspar Farewell; #1209 (Carton 17)
    - Stanford Quinquennial I; #1213 (Carton 17)
    - Burstein Birth Announcement; #1214 (Carton 17)
    - Stanford Quinquennial II; #1215 (Carton 17)
    - Chuang/Lacy Wedding#1216 (Carton 17)
    - Middlebrook/ Sugano Wedding; #1217 (Carton 17)
    - Caspar Broadside, Stanford; #1228 (Carton 17)
    - QNL Winter 2000/2001; #1235 (Carton 17)
    - Stanford Christmas; #1237 (Carton 17)
    - Rena Rosenwasser, Kelsey Street Press; #1243 (Carton 17)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Winter Meeting; #1259 (Carton 17)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Christmas; #1262 (Carton 17)
  - Job files, 2001
    - Western Pictures; #1208 (Carton 17)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Fall; #1218 (Carton 17)
    - June 16 Open House; no number (Carton 17)
    - Bancroft Award; no number (Carton 17)
    - Kircher Postcard; no number (Carton 17)
    - Typothethetae Lunch, no number (Carton 17)
    - RBMS Guidebook; no number (Carton 17)
    - Mankas Inverness Lodge; no number (Carton 17)
    - Gold Rush Book Fair Adv.-QNL; no number (Carton 17)
    - QNL Spring 2001; no number (Carton 17)
    - Louise Russell Card; no number (Carton 17)
    - Deborah Caperton Jewelry; no number (Carton 17)
    - Mankas Libation List; no number (Carton 17)
    - FAMSF Poster Bid; no number (Carton 17)
    - Von Dem Busshe In Memoriam; no number (Carton 17)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Keepsake Series; no number (Carton 17)
    - Book Club Postcard Exlibris/ Exhibit; no number (Carton 17)
    - Wayzgoose; #1308 (Carton 17)
    - Wanderly Business Cards; #1303 (Carton 17)
    - Norheim and Yost; #1320 (Carton 17)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Bookmark; # 1331 (Carton 17)
    - QNL Bid 2000-2001; #1316 (Carton 17)
    - Long and Levit Christmas Card; no number (Carton 17)
    - QNL; no number (Carton 17)
    - Matt Phillips-The Magic; no number (Carton 17)
    - Yellowstone Art Museum Auction; no number (Carton 17)
    - Marlene Saritzky Moving Card; #1306 (Carton 17)
    - Zapfest; #1198 (Carton 18)
    - Groth Wedding; # 1205 (Carton 18)
    - Stanford Anchor Brewery; # 1207 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Eps; #1227 (Carton 18)
    - Jack Bacon/President Fold Book; #1230 (Carton 18)
    - Matt Philips Announcement Card; #1231 (Carton 18)
    - Chez Panisse; #1234 (Carton 18)
    - Stanford Xmas; #1236 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Annual Meeting; #1241 (Carton 18)
    - Mills/Sanders Invitations; #1249 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Newsletter; #1250 (Carton 18)
    - FAMSF Invitations, Logan coll.; #1255 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Newsletter - Fall; #1264 (Carton 18)
  - Job files, 2002
    - Julianne Balmain Business Card; #1222 (Carton 18)
    - William H. Filter Business Cards; #1292 (Carton 17)
    - Mills Crad- Kaldewey; #1223 (Carton 18)
    - Peterson Memorial Bookclub; #1224 (Carton 18)
    - REAL Lead Archive (Carton 18)
    - Hormone Derange Specimen Book (Carton 18)
    - Filter Deep Food Xmas Coasters; #1286 (Carton 18)
    - Bill Wyer/Shakespeare (Carton 18)
    - Joan Wyer Card 2001 and 2002; #1279 (Carton 18)
    - AB Guthrie Jr. Poem; #1293 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Exhibition Announcement; #1294 (Carton 18)
    - Schoyers Books; #1298 (Carton 18)
    - Holtzman New Year Card; #1301 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Newsletter; #1310 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Newsletter - Fall; #1309 (Carton 18)
    - Wayzgoose Keepsake; #1307 (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Passion of Christ; #1317 (Carton 18)
    - Bancroft Award and Plate/Lady; #1349 (Carton 18)
    - Hawthorne Terrace Parks; #1291 (Carton 18)
    - QNL NL (Carton 18)
    - Heather Hodyson (Carton 18)
    - Koch New Year (Carton 18)
    - Duck Creek Martini; #1318 (Carton 18)
    - Susie Tomkins Book; #1277 (Carton 18)
    - WAYZGOOSE; #1304 (Carton 18)
    - Richard Seibert (Carton 18)
    - Hummingbird/Kamkar; #1232 (Carton 18)
    - Kamkar Poems; #1233 (Carton 18)
    - Richard Seibert (Carton 18)
    - Gleeson Library Associates/ Ricci; #1240 (Carton 18)
    - PRK Printers Proofs; #1252 (Carton 18)
    - Julianne Balmain Card; #1254 (Carton 18)
    - Darius Milhand/Mills Center for the Book; #1257 (Carton 18)
    - Jack Bacon/Golf; #1258 (Carton 18)
    - Mary Ann Haydn; #1244 (Carton 19)
    - Posada, Stanford U. Libraries; #1245 (Carton 19)
    - Franklin Allen Wedding; #1247 (Carton 19)
    - Posada Post Card; #1260 (Carton 19)
    - Stanford Xmas; #1278 (Carton 19)
    - Anna Simson; #1261 (Carton 19)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Xmas; #1263 (Carton 19)
    - Suzie Buell Cards; #1265 (Carton 19)
    - Matlack Birth Anne; #1266 (Carton 19)
  - Job files, 2002-2003
    - QNL Fall; no number (Carton 16)
    - Nina Wemyss Mondavi Business Cards; #1290 (Carton 16)
  - Job files, 2003
    - Stanford Xmas (Carton 19)
    - Crossings/Party 4th St.; #1270 (Carton 19)
    - Lisa Pongrace Wedding; #1282 (Carton 19)
    - Freda Koblick; #1281 (Carton 19)
    - Left Bank BC/CCC; #1287 (Carton 19)
    - Marlene Soritzky; #1284 (Carton 19)
    - Georgianna Greenwood; #1283 (Carton 19)
    - Point Lobos II Photo-Issue; #1285 (Carton 19)
    - Samora Dal Pogretto (Carton 19)
    - Zublin Letters (Carton 19)
    - Nancy Hoyt Card; #1288 (Carton 19)
    - Joan Wyer Xmas (Carton 19)
    - In Fine Poem/Filter (Carton 19)
    - Bancroft Resolution and Plate; #1350 (Carton 19)
    - Mary Day Card (Carton 19)
    - MPH Design (Carton 19)
    - Koch 60th Birthday (Carton 19)
    - Filter/Ferrani Deltino/ Poem (Carton 19)
    - Holtzman 40/50 and Business Cards (New) (Carton 19)
    - Mills Technology Invite (Carton 19)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Announcement Fall (Carton 19)
    - Arthur Bloch (Carton 19)
    - Book Club Post Card, Leonard Pitt (Carton 19)
    - Scharffenberger (Carton 19)
    - Lorrane Weiss (Carton 19)
    - Christopher Westfall/ Business Card (Carton 19)
    - Lenstra Poem; #1246 (Carton 19)
    - Carol Kaplan/ Bookplate; #1253 (Carton 19)
    - John Pope; #1256 (Carton 19)
    - Donald Oresman Book/ Short Takes; #1267 (Carton 19)
    - Karen Filter Card; #1268 (Carton 19)
    - Book Club Fine Print Card; Koch Party; #1269 (Carton 19)
    - Frangos/Fisher Wedding; #1272 (Carton 19)
    - Book Club/ Goines Cookbook Announcement; #1273 (Carton 19)
    - Anselmo Vigne; #1275 (Carton 19)
    - Friedman/Misch Cohen Memorial; #1280 (Carton 19)
    - Crossings/Prospectus; #1271 (Carton 19)
  - Job files, 2004
    - Rox. Announcement Club (Carton 19)
    - Gleeson Library Associates 2004 Announcement, Peter Pauper Press (Carton 19)
    - Studio Diana/ Certificate (Carton 19)
    - Bookclub Postcard ABE Lerner (Carton 19)
    - Grolier Club (Carton 19)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Remit Eps Plates (Carton 19)
    - Filter New Years Card 2003/4 at Carolyn Fraser (Carton 19)
    - Sandra Kirshenbaum Memorial (Carton 19)
    - 85 Gregory Whipple (Carton 19)
    - Oak Knoll Book Fair (Carton 19)
    - Helen Party/ Monica Strauss NYC (Carton 19)
    - Matt Phillips/ Black Cat Invite (Carton 19)
    - Kirk Robertson Show 2003-4 (Carton 19)
    - Theresa Whitehill Book (Carton 19)
    - Caf Fanny 20th Anniversary Broodside (Carton 19)
    - Christian Koch Journals (Carton 20)
    - Artist Book Council (Carton 20)
    - "In Fine" Reprint (Carton 20)
    - A Hero Comes Home (Carton 20)
    - Gleeson Library Associates Xmas Show (Carton 20)
  - Job files, 2005
    - Editions Koch Catalog (Carton 20)
    - Studio Diana Gift Cert. (Carton 20)
    - New Years Card (Carton 20)
    - Nancy Wickes Card 2004-5 (Carton 20)
    - BCC Rockwell Kent/ Bob Jackson Card (Carton 20)
    - Colophon Club (Carton 20)
    - David Dodd Bookplates (Carton 20)
    - Book Club Postcard/ Hand Bookbinders (Carton 20)
    - Onagh Stransky (Carton 20)
    - Koichi College of Environmental Design Alumni Awards (Carton 20)
    - Dan Stolpe; #1297 (Carton 20)
    - Stolpe, Book II (The Adversaries) (Carton 20)
    - Stolpe, Book III (Love and Death) (Carton 20)
    - Stolpe, Vol IV (Carton 20)
  - Job files, 2006
    - Richard Bucher cards (Carton 20)
    - Japanese Donor List, Sacramento State U (Carton 20)
    - Matt Phillips, Pas de Deux (Carton 20)
    - Hsia-Lee Wedding (Carton 20)
    - Website work - Koch (Carton 20)
  - Job files, miscellaneous, various dates
    - UNLV Rainmaker (Carton 20)
    - Chad (Hrs/Jobs) (Carton 20)
    - Cardoza-James (Carton 20)
    - MandH Type (Carton 20)
    - Maya Angelou Poem (A Brave and Startling Truth) (Carton 20)
    - Articles by P. Koch - various Years, #1160 (Carton 20)
    - Manifesto by P. Koch - "For Ourselves" Collection, 1973; #1153 (Carton 20)
    - Resumes - various years; #1161 (Carton 20)
    - Getty Conference; #1417 (Carton 20)
    - Literature on Book Centers, School Programs; #1416 (Carton 20)
    - Watermark - P. Koch; #1414 (Carton 20)
    - Nevada/Ode to the Bee;#1413 (Carton 20)
    - Bee Book Project - grant application; #1413 (Carton 20)
    - S. Graph Article 1987; #1411 (Carton 20)
    - Pressmans Ink Manual Article; #1412 (Carton 20)
    - Pentagram Press Corresp. 1976; #1404 (Carton 20)
    - Montana Centennial; #1399 (Carton 20)
    - PBI Ink Manufacturer; #1396 (Carton 20)
    - Misc. Desktop Notes; #1395 (Carton 20)
    - Anchor and Acorn Press; #1398 (Carton 20)
    - Whos Who; #1408 (Carton 20)